sp1: (Fukuko) A thin life
sp2: (Sanada) If there is something I can change, then sp2: I would like to change it.
sp2: Such a life
sp3: (Yamanaka) Don't give up easily
sp3: Anyone can shine anytime
(MC) Anyone can shine at any time.
He's around 40, but he's an eternal boy at heart...
sp2: What? A dream? (MC) Everyone from Eternal Boys.
♬～
sp3: From today sp3: These 6 members are an idol group
sp3: Eternal Boys
sp1: 6 people... sp3: Yes
sp2: Um, sorry for being so quick, but sp2: I...
(Asai) But if you're just going to make a normal idol.
Do you collect teenagers? We are old men
sp3: Good question, huh?
sp3: The concept of Eternal Boys is
sp3: “Anyone can shine anytime sp3:”
sp3: That's why sp3: Old men like us
sp3: Become an idol sp3: I want to prove it
sp2: Um... sp3: Actually...
sp3: This was left behind by the previous president in his final moments.
sp3: This is a special project.
sp3: I want to show you sp3: the scenery that my predecessor couldn't see.
sp3: Please... please lend me your strength.
♬～
sp3: We've arrived. This is the training camp.
Why is there a training camp here (Imagawa)?
sp3: Until your debut, here sp3: I want you to work hard on your lessons.
sp3: Yes, don't lose it
sp3: I'm a good adult so I don't set a curfew.
sp3: Lights out at 24 o'clock
sp3: The electricity will be forcibly turned off, so sp3: Be careful.
sp3: see
sp3: Let's go.
sp3: When I get back, the key is here (Imagawa) Yes.
sp3: Meals are served in the morning and at night.
sp3: Morning hours are from 7:00 to 9:00 sp3: Nights are from 19:00 to 21:00
sp3: There's only one bath, so sp3: Should I go to a public bath?
sp3: Please consult each other and make compromises.
(Asai) Wow what? This looks so delicious!
Gyoza (Ishida) has a good nutritional balance.
Who is making it?
Call the chef sp3: Chef?
sp3: Well, a chef...
sp3: Nikolai
♬～
(Asakura) I'm the chef, Nikolai.
"eagle, I"?
sp3: Nikolai Asakura
sp3: Besides cooking sp3: He also takes care of us.
(Asai) is a really good-looking guy.
ignore? sp3: I'm shy
(Asai) Even though she's blonde? sp3: Let's eat Hey, let's eat
sp3: Well, let's have it (Asai)!
(Asai) This is scary. This sp3: Delicious.
Delicious! Huh? Is it dangerous?
terrible! terrible?
(Imagawa) Yeah, it’s delicious! sp3: Nikolai it's delicious
(Asai) Seriously delicious!
(Kakizaki) Are you there? sp2: Ah yes
(Imagawa) It’s dangerous, right?
sp3: Ishida, take the salad sp2: Thank you
(Imagawa) You eat a lot (Asai) Issy
How many gyoza did you eat? It's so delicious!
I want to eat fried rice!
fried rice fried rice
(Imagawa) Fried rice is terrible.
sp3: Nikolai delicious
♬～
sp2: (coughing)
sp3: Are you okay?
sp2: Why...
sp3: Because we're friends now.
(Imagawa) Do you need water? sp2: Thank you
Office workers don't have the stamina sp2: Sorry.
sp3: Sanada
♬～
sp3: With this member sp3: I want to see more scenery
(Asai) Hahahaha! I agree
sp3: Don't laugh, I'm going home. Look (Imagawa) I'm hungry.
(Asai) Eat meat! (Imagawa) Good meat.
(Ishida) A legendary national idol who debuted 20 years ago.
Gentlemen's debut song ⚟♬ "Shall We Dance"
sp3: Eternal Boys The first step is sp3: Copy this completely
sp3: Post a video of yourself dancing (Imagawa/Asai) Oh!
I tried dancing!
⚟♬～
♬～
(Asai) Dangerous! sp2: Sorry
(Asai) Hahahaha
sp2: Sorry, it's my first time, so I can't help it.
Oh yeah, there's still a month until the shooting date.
sp2: Sorry
sp3: Too bad I'm leaving soon (Kakizaki) I have to work too.
sp3: You guys sp3: Go home before you miss dinner.
(Asai) Hey! I'm tired! sp3: Good job
(Kakizaki) Thank you for your hard work (Ishida) Thank you for your hard work
sp2: Thank you for your hard work
(Imagawa) Okay, I'll give you two some secret training.
(Asai) Oh, then I'll help too sp2: But food...
Okay, let's eat something later (Asai) Okay, let's start with the chorus.
sp2: yes
(Asai) 5 6 7 8…
１ ２ ３…
(Asai) It's already three minutes, right? (Ishida) 9 seconds left
8 7… (Imagawa) I’m hungry.
(Ishida) 5 4 3 2 1
I'll enjoy having this
Yummy
Ramen at this time of day is the best
sp2: It's really the best ramen I've ever had sp2:
(Asai) Hey, Sanayan, you're too excited.
Hehehehe
sp2: (crying)
what up? what up? what up?
sp2: No, eating food with other people is sp2: delicious.
sp2: I was like this kind of youth sp2: I thought I couldn't do it anymore.
Oh... it's scary! What happened all of a sudden?
You can have youth at any age. This is it.
Hahahahahahaha
sp2: yes
How about I go take a shower first? I'm fine, I have something to do.
No, it's already past 12 o'clock.
Huh? Hehehe
What? That guy
⚟♬～
♬～
Issy isn't getting better?
I can't do it if I try.
sp2: Sorry, it's just me after all sp2: You're holding me back.
What's that? I'm your senior, so it's okay.
That's right, we've only just begun.
sp2: Yes, thank you, let's watch it again.
It's getting better
(Imagawa) Look, it's getting better sp2: Thank you.
(Imagawa) His hands are well made (Asai) Or rather, Mr. Kakizaki...
(Laughter) (Kakizaki) That's true.
that! Would you like to stop now? That kind of familiarity
(Imagawa) Huh? I'm serious
I'm here to be an idol.If you just want to play friends.
It's a nuisance, so please do it elsewhere.
(Kakizaki) Ishida Isn't that wrong?
Is something wrong?
Generally speaking, the reason why Sanada-san never improves is that
Maybe it's because the two of you are spoiling each other like that.
I think so (Imagawa) huh? We are different...
(Asai) Alright, alright, Ima-chan, calm down.
What is it? Getting to know each other is getting to know each other.
You may be trying hard, but you can't do it.
I hope it gets better from now on
Let's stop!
sp2: As expected...
sp2: I'm the only one out of place.
sp2: In the first place, I don't really want to be an idol sp2:
Do that again...
Could you please stop making excuses?
sp2: yes
sp2: stop
sp2: quit everything
(Imagawa) Sanayan (Asai) Sanayan!
♬～
sp3: Bad The meeting took a long time.
sp3: What's wrong?
(Asai) Sanayan... sp3: Sanada?
sp3: Find a replacement responsibly
sp3: That's no problem, right?
Because kids these days are a little different.
You complain easily and run away right away, right?
(Kakizaki) Sanada! Look carefully
Ishida sneaks out of the training camp every night to practice here.